ojas-gujnic.in 2018-06-28

# Ojas.guj.nic.in: Gujarat Govt Online Job Application: OJAS Bharti: Privacy Policy

###  [ High Court of Gujarat Recruitment 2018 for Assistant Posts (HC OJAS) ](http://www.ojas-gujnic.in/2016/01/high-court-of-gujarat-legal-assistants-11-vacancies.html)

High Court of Gujarat has published an advertisement for Recruitment for Assistant Posts 2018. Candidates who want to make their career i... 

##  Today's Popular Jobs 

  *   * 

###  Privacy Policy 

Here at www.ojas-gujnic.in, a privacy of visitors is extremely important. That’s why we are publishing this Privacy Policy page to make all the visitors know about the important terms about our privacy. This Privacy Policy page provides you the type of information we collect or receive at www.ojas-gujnic.in and how this information is used.

**Log Files:**

Like many other websites, www.ojas-gujnic.in also uses log files. Our log files includes your IP Addresses, Internet Service Provider, Browser (User Agent), Date/Time Stamp, referring/exit pages, number of clicks to analyse trends, track users’ movement around the site, gather demographic information to better administer the website.

IP Addresses and other information we collect are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons:**

Ojas makes use of cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on which user visit, customize Web Page content according to users browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookies:**

Google, As a third part vendor uses DoubleClick DART Cookies to serve ads on www.ojas-gujnic.in and many other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out the use of DART Cookies by visiting Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy by visiting the URL:  http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.

Some other Advertisement Partners may use cookies and Web Beacons. Our Advertising Partners are listed below:

Google Adsense

Media.net

Some other direct advertisers

These third-party Ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.ojas-gujnic.in sends directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP Address when this occurs.

Other Technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third -party ad networks to measure the effectiveness to their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.ojas-gujnic.in has no access/control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices Ojas’ privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
